{
    "subject": "resource/Butterfly_(Hartnett_novel)",
    "predicate": "ontology/author",
    "object": "resource/Sonya_Hartnett",
    "human_readable": "Sonya Hartnett wrote the novel Butterfly.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8938326835632324,
            "question": "What is the title of the novel written by Sonya Hartnett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8823719620704651,
            "question": "Who wrote the novel Butterfly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7348800897598267,
            "question": "Are there any other novels written by Sonya Hartnett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38431698083877563,
            "question": "What genre is the novel Butterfly likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32607701420783997,
            "question": "How has the novel Butterfly been received by critics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3229232728481293,
            "question": "What awards has Sonya Hartnett won for her writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3047660291194916,
            "question": "Where and when is the novel Butterfly set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19998936355113983,
            "question": "What is the main character's name in Butterfly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19368478655815125,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any themes explored in Butterfly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09702035039663315,
            "question": "Are there any film or television adaptations of Butterfly?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sonya Hartnett wrote the novel Butterfly.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7952_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about any themes explored in Butterfly?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7952_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main character's name in Butterfly?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7952_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where and when is the novel Butterfly set?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7952_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7952_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Sonya Hartnett is the author of the novel \"Butterfly.\" This information directly supports the statement in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}